Guide to the Time Inc. Corporate Administration Records 1853-2002 (bulk, 1929-1995) MS 3009-RG 5
New-York Historical Society
Time Inc. Corporate Administration Records
1853-2002 (bulk, 1929-1995)
New-York Historical Society
Time, inc.
MS 3009-RG 5
192.7 Linear feet in 195 record cartons and 3 flat boxes
The Corporate Administration Records contain files from the corporate-level offices and executives of Time Inc. Executives and offices represented include the president, chief executive officer, chairman of the board, and chairman of the executive committee; corporate secretary; the finance division including files from the treasurer and investor relations; executive vice presidents; vice presidents overseeing administration, international, communications, and newspaper acquisitions; and a director of international business. Staff represented include Roy E. Larsen, James A. Linen, Andrew Heiskell, Ralph P. Davidson, Reginald K. Brack, Jr., and Don Logan. Records document corporate strategic planning for Time Inc., corporate filings, investments in terms of Time Inc. shareholders or in regards to employee retirement accounts, and major acquisitions, sales, or mergers including the merger between Time Inc. and Warner Communications creating Time Warner. Records also include executive committee minutes, five-year plans, notary seals, patents owned by Time Inc., early printing agreements, and corporate books or other organizational records from affiliates and subsidiaries of Time Inc.
Access Restrictions
Open to qualified researchers with the exception of restricted materials. Restricted materials may include contracts and agreements between Time Inc., its subsidiaries, and third parties; records with personally identifiable information; and personnel records regarding performance reviews or terminations. Materials created within the past 35 years also may be subject to restriction on a case-by-case basis. Aside from the full series or subseries of restricted records, restricted materials separated from their series are located in Boxes R9, R15, R16, R17, R65, R66, R67.
Unreformatted audiovisual and digital material in the collection is not accessible. Audiovisual is restricted because of its fragility and because N-YHS has no equipment on which to play them. Please contact the curator of manuscripts at manuscripts@nyhistory.org for further information. Digital material is currently restricted from access in order to ensure that the digital files are not accidentally corrupted.
Materials are stored offsite and advance notice is required for use.
Accruals
Further additions to this finding aid are expected.
Arrangement Note
Organized into 13 series with additional subseries. Series II is listed out more fully as files from the top executives of the company range through several positions.
Series I. General Files
Series II.A. President, Chairman of the Executive Committee, and Vice-chairman of the Board: Roy E. Larsen Files
Series II.B. President, Chairman of the Board, and Chairman of the Executive Committee: James A. Linen Files
Series II.C. Chairman of the Board and Chief Executive Officer: Andrew Heiskell Files Series II.D. Office of the President and Chairman of the Board: Ralph P. Davidson Files
Series II.E. Chief Financial Officer, Executive Vice President, President and Chief Operating Officer: N. J. Nicholas, Jr. Files
Series II.F. President, Chairman of the Board, and Chief Executive Officer: Reginald K. Brack, Jr. Files
Series II.G. President, Chief Operating Officer, and Chief Executive Officer: Don Logan Files
Series II.H. Office of the President: Corporate Special Projects Staff: Edgar P. Smith Files
Series III. Corporate Secretary Files
Series IV. Finance Division Files
Series V. Corporate Strategy Files
Series VI. Executive Vice President Kelso Sutton Files
Series VII. Executive Vice President Donald J. Barr TIME Newstour '95 Planning Files
Series VIII. Office of the Vice President of Administration and International Files
Series IX. Vice President of Communications Peter Costiglio Files
Series X. Vice President of Corporate Planning Henry Luce III Files
Series XI. Vice President Otto Fuerbringer files on newspaper acquisition and development of a news wire service
Series XII. Vice President of Administrative Services Rosemarie Di Sapio Files
Series XIII. Director of International Business Development William S. Rukeyser Files
Historical Note
Corporate Administration at Time Inc. includes the president, chief executive officer, chairman of the board, and chairman of the executive committee; vice presidents whose function only seems to exist at the corporate level (Peter Costiglio); executives overseeing multiple areas of the company (Charles Bear); and staff on special assignment at the corporate level (Otto Fuerbringer and William Rukeyser). Corporate Administration also includes corporate finance, the corporate secretary, and corporate strategy staff.
Executives at Time Inc. often held multiple positions over time, or concurrently, and kept their files all together without separation by position or office. Executives sometimes held staff positions along with board positions. The corporate finance department included the treasurer and assistant treasurers. The corporate secretary often was also the comptroller.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Time Inc. in 2015.
Related Archival Materials Note
This finding aid relates to just one record group of the Time Inc. Records. For information about the other record groups and for overall information about the archives, please see the Guide to the Time Inc. Records (MS 3009). The Henry Luce Papers (MS 3014) were acquired with the Time Inc. Records. The collection of books acquired with the records are cataloged as the Time Inc. Reference Library.
Due to the small number of Roy Larsen files, it is probable that the majority of his records ended up in one of the Time Inc. assembled collections, such as the Time Inc. Subject Files (MS 3009-RG 1) and the Time Inc. Bio Files (MS 3009-RG 2), or in his donation to Harvard.
Files from J. Richard Munro while he was president of the Board and Chief Executive Officer of Time Inc. are located in his subject files in the Time Inc. Video Group Records (MS 3009-RG 41). His subject files spanned from his time as Video Group Vice President through CEO, but the majority related to his GVP role.
Additional records on all departments, offices, or staff can be found in the Time Inc. Subject Files (MS 3009-RG 1), the Time Inc. Bio Files (MS 3009-RG 2), the Time Inc. Reference Files (MS 3009-RG 3), and the Time Inc. Annex Files (MS 3009-RG 39).
Scope and Contents Note
The Corporate Administration Records contain files from the corporate-level offices and executives of Time Inc. Executives and offices represented include the president, chief executive officer, chairman of the board, and chairman of the executive committee; corporate secretary; the finance division including files from the treasurer and investor relations; executive vice presidents; vice presidents overseeing administration, international, communications, and newspaper acquisitions; and a director of international business.
Staff represented include Roy E. Larsen, one of the first employees of Time Inc., the first employee of Time magazine, and credited as the third most important person, after the cofounders, in building Time Inc. as a company; James A. Linen; Andrew Heiskell; Ralph P. Davidson; Reginald K. Brack, Jr.; and Don Logan. Executive staff files sometimes document their philanthropic or volunteer work outside of Time Inc., including with the Prince of Songkla University in Thailand, the American Corporate Aid for Lebanon Inc., the National Urban League, and St. Bernard's School. Corporate management primarily handled corporate strategic planning for Time Inc., required corporate filings, Time Inc. stock and other stock investments, and major acquisitions, sales, or mergers including the merger between Time Inc. and Warner Communications creating Time Warner. Of interest are internal memoranda distributed to the "War List" during World War II in Treasurer Charles Stillman's files.
The General Files include corporate-level records where the exact office of origination is not known, or the files are from several people or offices at the corporate executive level, but were grouped together by Time Inc. at some point. Records include stock certificates, five-year plans, notary seals, patents owned by Time Inc., printing agreements, and corporate books or other organizational records from affiliates and subsidiaries of Time Inc.
Appointment books; Certificates of incorporation; Consolidation and merger of corporations.; Corporations -- History.; Corporations -- New York (State) -- New York.; Corporation records.; Newspaper publishing -- United States; Organization files.; Patents; Printing industry; Publishers and publishing -- Management; Publishers and publishing -- New York (State) -- New York.; Radio stations -- Administration; Seals; Speeches (documents); Stock certificates.; Time, inc. -- Archives.; Time, inc. -- History.; Time, inc. -- Management.; Brack, Reginald K., Jr.; Davidson, Ralph P.; Heiskell, Andrew; Larsen, Roy E. (Roy Edward), 1899-; Levin, Gerald M.; Linen, James A.; Logan, Don, 1944-; Nicholas, N. J., Jr. (Nicholas J.), approximately 1940-; Sutton, Kelso; Time Warner, Inc.; Warner Communications Inc.
- Series I.A. General: Stock, 1929-1934, 1964; 5.1 Linear feet in 4 record cartons and 3 flat boxes
  Scope and Contents Note
  Stock includes canceled Time Inc. stock certificates, stock split ledgers listing the stockholder, account number, and shares owned; and stock books from which certificates were written.
  Arrangement Note
  Organized alphabetically by document format.
  - Stock Certificates, 1929-1930 (Offsite-box 4182, Folder 7)
  - Stock Certificates, 1929-1933 (Offsite-box 2047)
  - Stock Certificates, 1931 June-1933 June (Offsite-box 772)
  - Stock Certificates, 1933 June-September (Offsite-box 773)
  - Stock Certificates, 1933 September-1934 June, undated (Offsite-box 774)
  - Stock Split Ledgers, 1964 (Offsite-box 1789)
  - Stock Books: Time Inc., 1929-1933 (Offsite-box 2832)
  - Stock Books: March of the Years, 1933 (Offsite-box 2832)
  - Stock Books: March of Time, 1934-1935 (Offsite-box 2832)
- Series I.B. General: Bound Books of Sales or Acquisitions [RESTRICTED], 1962-1972; 3 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains books of bound documents pertaining to the sales or acquisitions of Time Inc. subsidiaries and divisions. According to a survey of the archives commissioned by the Time Inc. prior to the N-YHS acquisition of the materials, these books are all duplicates. Some books have staff names on them such as head of newspaper exploration Otto Fuerbringer, comptroller and assistant secretary John Harvey, and vice president and director of corporate development Edgar Baker. The series is restricted as contracts and agreements are bound together with other types of documents such as stock sales and articles of incorporation or dissolution.
  Arrangement
  Organized alphabetically by company name with arrangement imposed.
  - Eastex Packaging, Inc.: Loan agreement, 1965 (Offsite-box 4237, Item 1)
  - Hollister Newspaper Companies: Acquisition of assets, 1969 (Offsite-box 4235, Item 1)
  - Homemakers' Library League, Inc. and Family Publications Service, Inc., 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 4235, Item 2-3)
  - Little, Brown and Company: Acquisition, 1968 (Offsite-box 4235, Item 4-5)
  - Organizacion Editorial Novaro, S.A., 1966 (Offsite-box 4237, Item 2)
  - Pioneer Publishing Company: Stock acquisition, 1969 (Offsite-box 4236, Item 1)
  - President (Japan), 1963 (Offsite-box 4236, Item 2)
  - Silver Burdett Company: Acquisition, 1962 (Offsite-box 4236, Item 3)
  - Silver Burdett Company: Time Inc.-General Electric joint venture, 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 4236, Item 4)
  - Time Inc.: Stock split, 1964 (Offsite-box 4236, Item 7-8)
  - Time Inc.: Stock, 1964 (Offsite-box 4237, Item 3-4)
  - Time-Life Broadcast, Inc.: Sale: WFBM AM and FM, 1972 (Offsite-box 4236, Item 5-6)
  - Time-Life Broadcast, Inc.: Sale: WOOD AM and FM, 1972 (Offsite-box 4237, Item 5-6)
- Series I.C. General: Contract, Corporate, and Corporate Secretary Legal Files, 1853-1976 (bulk, 1929-1976); 7.25 Linear feet in 8 record cartons
  Contract, Corporate, and Corporate Secretary Legal Files are similar to the subseries Dead Companies, but were not included on the lists found with the transfer of Dead Companies to the Time Inc. Archives. These are a mix of files from defunct companies and old business arrangements made by Time Inc. and include acquisition and sale agreements, articles of incorporation and dissolution, meeting minutes, correspondence, publishing contracts, and title searches. The files come from Arnold Carlson as Controller (or Comptroller), John "Jack" Harvey as Comptroller, Peter Sheppe as Director of Administrative Services (Comptroller department), and Dean Chamberlain (business manager Time-Life International and then Corporate Circulation.) There are notes showing that some records are from the "Contract file"; files sent to Ronnie Biehl for the "Corp file"; and files from the "Corp Sec [Corporate Secretary] Legal file cabinet."
  This series includes extensive contract files from production of The March of Time. Records include leasing, financing, and distribution agreements along with correspondence from director Louis de Rochemont and Roy Larsen.
  The majority of records are restricted due to restrictions on contracts and agreements between Time Inc., its subsidiaries, and third parties. Open materials include articles of incorporation, board meeting minutes, correspondence, and title searches.
  Additional and more complete publishing agreements are in the subseries Printing Agreements.
  Organized alphabetically based on the original order.
  - Albuquerque Broadcasting [RESTRICTED], 1952-1957 (Offsite-box 612, Folder 1-7)
  - Aladdin and LTF [RESTRICTED], approximately 1957-1960 (Offsite-box 612, Folder 8-11)
  - Architectural Forum [RESTRICTED], 1941-1965 (Offsite-box 612-613)
    Includes records regarding Wilson H. Lee Company.
  - Barges-N. L. Wallace and C. L. Stillman [RESTRICTED], 1950-1963 (Offsite-box 613, Folder 4-6)
  - Blue Network Company [RESTRICTED], 1943-1948 (Offsite-box 613, Folder 7)
  - Cablemedia Services, Inc., 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 4233, Folder 1)
  - Cable Television of Rochester, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Offsite-box 4233, Folder 2)
  - Cascade Television of Rochester, Inc., 1973 (Offsite-box 4233, Folder 3)
  - Chicago title searches, 1853, 1875, 1888, 1898-1901 (Offsite-box 613, Folder 8-9)
  - Coast Cable Television Services, Inc., 1966-1970 (Offsite-box 4233, Folder 4-5)
  - Compania Editora, T. L. I. [RESTRICTED], 1951-1965 (Offsite-box 613, Folder 10-14)
    Regarding a Time Life International publishing agreement in Cuba.
  - Consolidated Television & Radio Broadcasters, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1956-1957 (Offsite-box 613)
  - Consolidated Television & Radio Broadcasters, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1956-1957 (Offsite-box 614, Folder 1-2)
  - Cornwall Co-Ax, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Offsite-box 4233, Folder 6)
  - Cuneo Press [RESTRICTED], 1929-1939 (Offsite-box 614, Folder 3-5)
    Includes records regarding publishing Architectural Forum and Fortune.
  - De Luxe Laboratories [RESTRICTED], 1946 (Offsite-box 614, Folder 6)
  - F-Miscellaneous [George A. Fuller Company] [RESTRICTED], 1956-1958 (Offsite-box 614, Folder 7)
  - Fresno Cable TV Co., Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Offsite-box 4233, Folder 7)
  - Fulfillment Corporation of America [RESTRICTED], 1948-1956 (Offsite-box 614, Folder 8)
  - Hay, John I. Co. [John I. Hay Company] [RESTRICTED], 1941-1952 (Offsite-box 614, Folder 9)
  - Hennepin Paper Co. [RESTRICTED], 1945-1948 (Offsite-box 614, Folder 10-11)
  - Hillcrest Oil Company [RESTRICTED], 1957-1962 (Offsite-box 614, Folder 12-13)
  - Lebanon Television Station (La Compagnie Libanaise de Television) [RESTRICTED], 1961-1963 (Offsite-box 614, Folder 14)
  - Life's Picture History of World War II [RESTRICTED], 1950-1951 (Offsite-box 614, Folder 15)
  - Old Life - Purchase [RESTRICTED], 1936-1941 (Offsite-box 614, Folder 16)
    Contains purchase agreements of the Life humor magazine in order to obtain the rights to use the title "Life."
  - Literary Digest: Purchase [RESTRICTED], 1922-1938 (Offsite-box 614, Folder 17)
    Includes trademark transfers.
  - Lubin, Eisner, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 614, Folder 18-19)
    Include records relating to Michigan Square Building and Printing Developments, Inc.
  - Lubin, Eisner, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 615, Folder 1)
  - L Miscellaneous [Joe Louis Enterprises, Inc.] [RESTRICTED], 1948 (Offsite-box 615, Folder 2)
  - Maine Seaboard Paper Company [RESTRICTED], 1937-1952 (Offsite-box 615, Folder 3-13)
  - Maine Seaboard Paper Company [RESTRICTED], 1940-1947 (Offsite-box 4232, Folder 1-3)
  - The March of Time: Distributors-Dissolution [RESTRICTED], 1935-1937 (Offsite-box 4232, Folder 4)
  - The March of Time: De Luxe Laboratories [RESTRICTED], 1934-1936 (Offsite-box 4232, Folder 5)
  - The March of Time: Garbo, Woman of Destiny [RESTRICTED], 1934 (Offsite-box 4232, Folder 6)
  - The March of Time: Movietonenews [RESTRICTED], 1934-1936 (Offsite-box 4232, Folder 7)
  - The March of Time: Pathe Film Corporation [RESTRICTED], 1934-1942 (Offsite-box 4232, Folder 8)
  - The March of Time: RCA Contract [RESTRICTED], 1937-1953 (Offsite-box 4232, Folder 9)
  - The March of Time: RKO Building [RESTRICTED], 1934-1935 (Offsite-box 4232, Folder 10)
  - The March of Time: RKO Radio Pictures [RESTRICTED], 1935-1952 (Offsite-box 4232, Folder 11-13)
  - The March of Time: Theatres [RESTRICTED], 1935 (Offsite-box 4232, Folder 14-15)
  - The March of Time: Time Inc. Contract [RESTRICTED], 1934-1935 (Offsite-box 4232, Folder 16)
  - The March of Time: Time Inc. with March of Time, Limited [RESTRICTED], 1936-1945 (Offsite-box 4232, Folder 17)
  - The March of Time: Twentieth Century Fox [RESTRICTED], 1942-1952 (Offsite-box 4232, Folder 18-20)
  - The March of Time: Miscellaneous contracts [RESTRICTED], 1935-1952 (Offsite-box 4232, Folder 21-22)
  - The March of the Years, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1934-1949 (Offsite-box 4232, Folder 23)
  - Michigan Square Building [RESTRICTED], 1941-1953 (Offsite-box 615, Folder 14-15)
  - N-Miscellaneous [National Broadcasting Company, Inc.] [RESTRICTED], 1954 (Offsite-box 615, Folder 16)
  - Pan American Capital Corporation [RESTRICTED], 1956-1961 (Offsite-box 615, Folder 17)
  - Publishers Printing Company [RESTRICTED], 1945-1948 (Offsite-box 615, Folder 18)
    Regarding the publishing of Architectural Forum.
  - Publishers Printing-Rogers Kellogg Corporation [RESTRICTED], 1930-1943 (Offsite-box 615, Folder 19)
    Regarding the publishing of Architectural Forum, and includes agreements with The Reader's Digest.
  - Readers Digest [RESTRICTED], 1941-1950 (Offsite-box 615, Folder 20)
  - Richmond Cable Television, Inc., 1965 (Offsite-box 4233, Folder 8)
  - Rogers & Manson Corporation [RESTRICTED], 1932-1959 (Offsite-box 615, Folder 21-22)
    Includes Architectural Forum 1932 Certificate of Incorporation.
  - Rogers & Manson Corporation [RESTRICTED], 1932-1959 (Offsite-box 616, Folder 1)
  - Time-Fortune Corporation [RESTRICTED], 1932-1936 (Offsite-box 616, Folder 2)
  - Time Incorporated Book Clubs, Inc., 1973 (Offsite-box 4233, Folder 9)
  - Time-Life Broadcast, Inc.: General [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Offsite-box 4233, Folder 10)
  - Time-Life Broadcast, Inc.: American Cable Television, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1966 (Offsite-box 4233, Folder 11)
  - Time-Life Broadcast, Inc.: Ashtabula Cable TV, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1967-1972 (Offsite-box 4233, Folder 12)
  - Time-Life Broadcast, Inc.: Auburn Cablevision, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Offsite-box 4233, Folder 13)
  - Time-Life Broadcast, Inc.: Brentwood Co. [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Offsite-box 4233, Folder 14)
  - Time-Life Broadcast, Inc.: Bridgeport Community Antennae TV Company, 1966 (Offsite-box 4233, Folder 15)
  - Time-Life Broadcast, Inc.: Certificate of Amendment, 1972 (Offsite-box 4233, Folder 16)
  - Time-Life Broadcast, Inc.: Community Antennae Television System of Century Cable Co. [RESTRCITED], 1972 (Offsite-box 4233, Folder 17)
  - Time-Life Broadcast, Inc.: DuMont-Time [RESTRICTED], 1961 (Offsite-box 4233, Folder 18)
  - Time-Life Broadcast, Inc.: Hightower Telesystems, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1966-1969 (Offsite-box 4233, Folder 19-21)
  - Time-Life Broadcast, Inc.: Indiana Cable TV, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Offsite-box 4233, Folder 22)
  - Time-Life Broadcast, Inc.: Manhattan Cable, 1968 (Offsite-box 4233, Folder 23)
  - Time-Life Broadcast, Inc.: Marion Cable Television, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1966-1972 (Offsite-box 4233, Folder 24)
  - Time-Life Broadcast, Inc.: Nevada, 1967 (Offsite-box 4233, Folder 25)
  - Time-Life Broadcast, Inc.: Port Arthur Cablevision [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Offsite-box 4233, Folder 26)
  - Time-Life Broadcast, Inc.: Rochester, Inc./Coaxial Systems, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1970-1973 (Offsite-box 4233, Folder 27-28)
  - Time-Life Broadcast, Inc.: Securities and Exchange Commission application, 1972 (Offsite-box 4234, Folder 1)
  - Time-Life Broadcast, Inc.: Shows Inc. incorporation, 1966 (Offsite-box 4234, Folder 2)
  - Time-Life Broadcast, Inc.: Teleprompter Corporation [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Offsite-box 4234, Folder 3)
  - Time-Life Broadcast, Inc.: Time-Life/Columbia Cable TV, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Offsite-box 4234, Folder 4)
  - Time-Life Cable Communications, Inc. and Sentinel Communications, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Offsite-box 4234, Folder 5)
  - Time-Life Cablevision of Des Moines, Inc., 1972 (Offsite-box 4234, Folder 6)
  - Time-Life Cablevision of Louisville, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1971-1973 (Offsite-box 4234, Folder 7)
  - Time-Life Cablevision of Richmond, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Offsite-box 4234, Folder 8)
  - Time-Life International (Curacao) N.V. [RESTRICTED], 1961-1967 (Offsite-box 4234, Folder 9)
  - TLF Broadcasters, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1957 (Offsite-box 4234, Folder 10)
  - TLF Broadcasters, Inc., 1961 (Offsite-box 4234, Folder 11)
  - Truman memoirs [RESTRICTED], 1953-1960 (Offsite-box 616, Folder 3-4)
    Records and agreements regarding purchasing the publishing rights to Harry S. Truman's memoirs.
  - Valley Cablevision, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Offsite-box 4234, Folder 12)
  - W.F.T. Investments, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Offsite-box 4234, Folder 13)
  - Whitney, Courtney (General) [RESTRICTED], 1954-1963 (Offsite-box 616, Folder 5)
    Records and agreements regarding purchasing the publishing rights to his work about Douglas MacArthur.
  - Windsor, Duke of [RESTRICTED], 1947-1951 (Offsite-box 616, Folder 6)
    Includes copyright registrations from several countries for articles written by the Duke of Windsor.
- Series I.D. General: Dead Companies Files [RESTRICTED], 1946-1979; 3 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
  Dead Companies contains a group of materials accompanied by a transfer list naming the companies included. Records include acquisition and sale agreements, operation agreements, certificates of incorporation and dissolution, articles of merger, correspondence, and other corporate documents. The files come from Charles Bear as Secretary, Barry Zorthian as Vice President, John "Jack" Harvey as Comptroller, and Peter Sheppe as Director of Administrative Services (Comptroller department). There is cross-over of company names with the subseries Subsidiary Corporate Books.
  Organized alphabetically with lists of the companies at the front.
  - Lists, undated (Offsite-box 606, Folder 1)
  - Aladdin / LTF, 1972 (Offsite-box 606, Folder 2)
  - American Health Corporation, 1973-1979 (Offsite-box 606, Folder 3)
  - Andre Deutsch Limited, 1969-1972 (Offsite-box 606, Folder 4)